Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
* Our world's about to break *
* Tormented and upset *
* We're lost from when we wake *
* With no way to go back *
* I'm standing on my own *
* But now I'm not alone *
* Always we will fight as one *
* Till the battle's won *
* With evil on the run *
* We never come undone *
* Assemble, we are strong *
* Forever fight as one *
Display chronal archive 001944.
Key word: Rogers.
Loading.
News from the front.
As the Hydra war machine expands its reach,
one by one, the nations of Europe
fall under its shadow.
None so far have withstood the onslaught.
But Allied soldiers from across
the globe stand together,
and as the world goes to war,
we recount the tale of
Steve Rogers,
the man who would become Captain America.
Although young Rogers was
too frail for combat,
his fighting spirit
wouldn't give up.
He volunteered for a secret
military experiment
and, with the help of the country's
finest scientists,
was transformed into the
world's first
super soldier.
And now he fights alongside
the Allies
as a symbol of freedom and
liberty for all the world.
Even now, Cap is leading the charge
against the dreaded Red Skull
and his Hydra forces.
Good luck, Captain America,
wherever you are.
We're sitting ducks out here.
Howlett, I need recon!
I'm working on it, bub.
This is the end of the line, boys.
Our job is to take down
Hydra's science base,
and we've already got a man
on the inside to get us in.
Now let's go show the Red
Skull that his day is over!
Lieutenant Strucker.
Report.
Herr Skull, the Allies
have found the fortress.
Captain America is with them.
Send your best regiment out to confront him.
He will defeat them, of course,
but it will give us time
to prepare the specimens.
This will be the perfect test.
Sorry, Sarge. It's one of a kind.
Jack.
Jack!
Uh-- You're late.
Any trouble inside, Bucky?
There are Hydra
soldiers everywhere.
I couldn't get into the
lower levels on my own
without raising the alarm,
but I know the way.
Not a problem.
The stealth portion of this
mission is officially over.
I'll knock.
Must be the welcoming committee.
I've got this covered.
You know what, Cap?
I change my mind. You get this one.
Okay, we've seen some
weird stuff in this war,
but what is that? I don't know.
One of Zola's experiments, maybe.
Whatever it is, it's angry.
Back off, ugly!
Cap!
You want me, monster?
Here I am.
Let's keep moving.
Yeah. Sure.
No use dwelling on the big
monster that almost ate us.
Smart bombs.
Nerve gas.
Germ warfare.
Okay, this is creeping me out.
Hydra's been working on
this stuff for years.
Any one of these things could
mean big trouble for the Allies.
That's why we're here, Bucky.
No matter what, we're taking
down the Skull once and for all.
What in the world is this, Cap?
I'm not so sure this
is from our world.
You may come out now, Captain.
I know you are here.
You have arrived just in
time to witness history.
Ah, you always get me caught.
Oh, please, Captain.
Even if you were to survive,
your partner would not.
Still doing Zemo's
dirty work, Skull?
No. No.
I have stopped looking for
the relics of this world.
Today, I take the
power of another one.
Ancient Norse mythology
told of a realm
of supernaturally powerful beings.
And all myths have
some basis in truth.
This cave was the location
of one gateway to that realm.
The Norse called it Bifrost--
the Rainbow Bridge.
Picture an army of
mythological beasts
unleashed upon the battlefield.
The Allies won't even comprehend
the forces that are
destroying them.
Looks like your doggy there
would rather gnaw on
you than us, Skull.
We have ways of
guiding their choices.
What have you done?
What have I done?
I have won this war, Captain.
Open the portal!
Now? Not yet.
Sir, we've locked on to a specimen.
Increase power. Bring it through!
Cap? I see it.
Now!
No! Nooo!
Skull!
Get to the portal.
Do whatever it takes.
Just close it!
Yah!
I had hoped to test this blade
on the great Captain America.
You are not worthy to face me.
Is it because I have
more hair than you?
Don't feel bad, Strucker.
Maybe when you get older,
it'll grow in.
Sloppy technique.
You shave your head with that thing, too?
That would explain a lot.
Come on, soldier. Think.
Time to go home.
Bucky, now!
No. No! You have
destroyed everything!
I will have my revenge
on you and the world!
We have to get out of here!
Not this time, partner.
We're not letting
him get away again.
There he is. Bucky, stay here.
Secure the fortress.
I got your back, Cap!
Bucky, I told you to st-- Yeah, I know.
But we're partners, right?
Let's finish this.
It's over, Skull.
Finally, we agree.
Goodbye, Captain America!
No!
There's not enough time!
Bucky, jump for it!
I can't!
Cap!
Hang on, Bucky!
Sorry, Cap.
Stow that talk. We'll make it.
No, I mean, sorry,
but the world needs Captain
America more than Bucky.
No!
No! Bucky!
Today, Earth's mightiest hero
fell in the line of duty.
Farewell, Captain America,
wherever you are.
No.
Not where. When.
Let's keep moving.
Yeah. Sure.
No use dwelling on the big
monster that almost ate us.
Forward to time index 3.2.
I will have my revenge
on you and the world!
We have to get out of here!
Not this time, partner.
We're not letting
him get away again.
Ahead 7.25.
I've got your back, Cap!
Ahead .39.
No! No! Bucky!
Mmm. Manual control.
Time disturbance in progress.
Initiate chronal jump
to Damocles base.
Report. Temporal disturbances
reaching critical levels.
The fabric of time-space is in
the process of rupturing.
Show me.
My entire time line--
all of reality is being wiped out,
and it's all because of you.
My travels into the past
suggest that you are the link,
Captain America.
Some moment in your past
heralds the end of the future.
Something to do with you.
But I saw you
meet your end in the 20th century.
How can you be responsible?
Unless...
Damocles, scan all surviving
records from the 21st century.
Executing.
Freeze image.
Of course.
I did not conquer the Earth
just to see it wiped
from existence.
Damocles, prepare the fleet for time jump.
All ships begin
trans-temporal jump.
Sir, we don't have the coordinates.
There's not enough time to--
Never tell me there's
not enough time.
Time coordinates accepted.
Jump in progress.
Where is Princess Ravonna?
She's boarding now, my Lord.
My love, what is happening?
Why are we leaving?
Ravonna, no!
Damocles, now!
Update. The time dissolution
has slowed
but is still in effect.
I'll save you, my love.
I'll save our entire time line,
even if I have to conquer
this time to do it.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today